glossi.com 2014-11-20

# Slipp.it - Privacy Policy

#### Effective Date: October 9, 2012

### Scope of this Policy

In this Privacy Policy ("Policy"), we describe the information, including personal information, that we collect from visitors to our website, www.slipp.it (the "Site") and all services offered or made available through our Site, mobile application/services, and software provided on or in connection with the service (collectively, the "Services"). At Slipp.it, users may discover, self-publish, and share magazines that they or others create through our Site. By visiting our Site and/or using our Services, you agree that your information will be handled as described in this Policy, which is incorporated by reference into our Terms of Service.

Please read this Policy carefully. A large portion of our Site is user-generated content. Unless you designate otherwise, certain of the content that you post to the Site not only will be viewable by other users but also will be available for use by other users.

### What Information Do We Collect About You and Why?

The information we collect from you allows you to log into our Site, helps us provide our Services to you, send you information or content you may be interested in, and connect you with other users. We also use this information to personalize and continually improve our Site and our Services.

 _Information We Collect Directly From You._ We collect information directly from you when you log into our Site and use our Services. We require users to create an account with us to be able to use certain features of our Site. You may create an account directly with us, use an account that you created through another Thisnext website, or log onto our Site through certain third-party social networking sites (e.g., Facebook, Twitter), which may change from time-to-time. If you create an account with us, we will collect certain information, including personal information about you, such as your name, email address, and other contact information. We also collect any information that you chose to post to our Site. Please see the section entitled "User Generated Content" for additional information.

_Information We Collect from Third Parties._ If you log into our Site through a third-party social network, you will use the credentials that you have established with that network. The third-party social networking site, not us, controls the information that is requested during the log on process. If you log on through a social networking site, you may continue to use your user name and password from that Site. When you log into our Services through a third-party, we will request certain permissions from you, which vary based on the particular third-party site. For example, when you sign into our Services through Facebook Connect, we request your permission to: access your basic information, including your name, profile picture, gender, list of friends, user ID, and any other information that you have chosen to make public; post to your wall; send email directly to you; and access your data at any time even if you are not using Facebook. If you allow us to have access to this information, then we will have access to this information even if you have chosen not to make it public. For information about how a particular third-party social networking site may disclose your information, including any information that you make public, please consult that third-party's privacy policy. We do not have any control over how a third-party discloses the information that you provide to it. We store the information that you provide to us along with other information that we collect from and about you.

_Information We Collect Automatically._ We may use cookies, web beacons, and other automated devices to collect information about you when you visit our Site and use our Services. Specifically, we may collect the following information about your use of the Site via these technologies: your browser type and operating system; web pages you view; links you click; your IP address; your interaction with the Application; length of time you are logged in to our Site and our Services; the friends that you invite to use our Services; and website visited before our Site. We also may collect the following information about your use of the Application: iPhone device ID; location and language information; device name and model; operating system type, name, and version; your interaction with the Application; and the length of time that you are logged into our Application. Please see the section "What About Cookies" below for more information about our use of cookies. We may use the information gathered through these methods in anonymous or aggregated form to analyze ways to improve our Site or Services. This information is also associated with your username and may be combined with other information, including personally identifiable information that we collect about you.

### How Do We Use Your Information?

We use the information that we collect from and about you, including personal information (collectively, "information") for the following purposes:

  * To provide our Services to you, to communicate with you regarding use of our Services, and for other customer service purposes.
  * To tailor the content and information that we may send or display to you, and to otherwise personalize your experiences while using the Site or our Services.
  * To improve our Site and Services by providing personalized experiences, personalized help and instructions.
  * For research purposes.
  * For marketing and advertising purposes; for example, we may use your information to display targeted advertisements to you on our Site; we also may use your email address to email you news and newsletters, special offers, and promotions; we also may use the information that we learn about you to determine where to assist us in advertising our Services on third party websites.
  * To better understand how users access and use our Site and Services, both on an aggregated and individualized basis, for the purposes of improving our Site and Services and responding to user desires and preferences.
  * We will use and access this information for the purposes described in this section and as discussed below.

### When Do We Share Your Information?

We do not sell or rent our users' personal information for a third-party's own marketing purposes. As described below, we may share your information, including your personal information, with other visitors to our Site as well as with third parties to assist us in operating our Site and providing our Services.

_Other Visitors to Our Site and our Services._ Slipp is an open network. That means that any information that you post to our Site and our Services, unless you choose to make it private, will be viewable by other visitors to our Site. Your social networking username and profile picture also will be viewable by other visitors to our Site. In addition, except where prohibited by law and subject to your designating a restriction, other users of our Site and our Services may re-use the content that you post to the Site and our Services. 

_Affiliates._ We may disclose the information we collect from you to our affiliates or subsidiaries; however, if we do so, their use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information will be subject to this Policy. Service Providers. We may disclose the information we collect from you to third party vendors, service providers, contractors or agents who perform functions on our behalf.

_Business Transfers._ If we are acquired by or merged with another company, if substantially all of our assets are transferred to another company, or as part of a bankruptcy proceeding, we may transfer the information we have collected from you to the acquiring company.

_In Response to Legal Process._ We also may disclose the information we collect from you in order to comply with the law, a judicial proceeding, court order, or other legal process, such as in response to a court order or a subpoena.

_To Protect Us and Others._ We also may disclose the information we collect from you where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, or violations of our Terms of Use or this Policy.

_Aggregate and Anonymized Information._ We may share aggregate or anonymized information about users with third parties for marketing, advertising, research or similar purposes. For example, if we display advertisements on behalf of a third-party, we may share aggregate, demographic information with that third party about the users to whom we displayed the advertisements.

### What About Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies?

We and our third-party service providers use cookies, web beacons (including clear GIFs), Flash LSOs, and similar technologies to track user activity and collect Site data. We may combine this data with the personal information we have collected from you.

**Cookies.** Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser. We and our third-party service providers use "cookies" on our Site to, among other things, better serve you with tailored information and facilitate your ongoing access to and use of the Site. There are two types of cookies: session-based and persistent cookies. In addition, we also allow vendors to use cookies on our Site.

**Session Cookies**. Session cookies exist only during an online session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser or turn off your computer. We use session cookies to allow our systems to uniquely identify you during a session or while you are logged in to the Site. This allows us to process your online transactions and requests and verify your identity, after you have logged in, as you move through our Site.

**Persistent cookies**. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you have closed your browser or turned off your computer. We use persistent cookies to track aggregate and statistical information about user activity, which may be combined with other user information.

**Third-Party Cookies**. We also engage third parties to track and analyze non-personal and personal information to serve advertisements. To do so, we may permit third parties to apply cookies to users of our Site, where permitted by law, and, subject to your right to opt-out through the Network Advertising Initiative (as discussed below). We use the data collected by such third parties to help us administer and improve the quality of the Site and to analyze site usage. Such third parties may combine the information that we provide about you with other information that they have collected. 

_Disabling Cookies_. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer you can edit your browser options to block them in future. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your computer from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Visitors to our Site who disable their web browsers' ability to accept cookies will be able to browse the Site; however, some Site features, such as the ability to edit Slipps will not function if you disable cookies. 

**Local Storage Objects.** We and our third party service providers may use Flash Local Storage Objects ("Flash LSOs") TO store your Site preferences, to personalize your visit or to display content based upon what you view on our Site. Flash LSOs are different from browser cookies because of the amount and type of data stored. In addition, you cannot control, delete or disable the acceptance of Flash LSOs through your browser. For more information on Flash LSOs, or to learn how to manage your settings for Flash cookies, go to the Adobe Flash Player Help Page, choose "Global Storage Settings Panel" and follow the instructions. To see the Flash LSOs currently on your computer, choose "Website Storage Settings Panel" and follow the instructions to review and, if you choose, to delete any specific Flash LSO. 

**Web Beacons, Pixel Tags and Other Technologies.** We use web beacons, such as clear GIFs, web bugs or pixel tags, which are tiny graphics with a unique identifier similar in function to cookies. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on your computer's hard drive, clear GIFs are embedded invisibly on web pages. We may use clear GIFs in connection with our Site to, among other things, track the activities of website visitors, help us manage content, and compile statistics about website usage. We and our third party service providers also use clear GIFs in HTML e-mails to our customers, to help us track e-mail response rates, measure the success of our marketing campaigns, identify when our e-mails are viewed and track whether our e-mails are forwarded. 

**Site Analytics.** As noted, we work with third-party service providers who use the technologies described in this section to conduct website analytics to help us track and understand how visitors use our Site. For example, we use a variety of third-party web analytics, to help us improve our Site's performance and user experiences. 

**Third-Party Ad Networks.** We may use third-parties such as network advertisers to serve advertisements on our Sites. Please see the section entitled "Advertising" for additional information about our practices and your choices with regard to receiving such advertisements. 

**Third-Party Applications.** Third-party applications may be available on our Site. The owners or providers of those third party applications may collect personally identifiable information from you. Their collection of information is bound by their own information collection policies and practices. We are not responsible for the collection and use of your information by third parties.

**Advertisements.** We display advertisements on our Site. Some of the advertisements are based on the collection of personal information and others are based on the collection of aggregate information. Please see the bottom of this section for opt-out information.

We use third-parties such as network advertisers to serve advertisements on our Site. Network advertisers are third-parties that display advertisements based on your visits to our Site and other websites you have visited. This enables us and these third-parties to target advertisements to you for products and services in which you might be interested. Third-party ad network providers, advertisers, sponsors and/or traffic measurement services may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (including clear GIFs), Flash LSOs and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content to you. These third party cookies and other technologies are governed by each third party's specific privacy policy, not this one. We may provide these third-party advertisers with information about your usage of our Site and our Services, both personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information.

**You may opt-out of many third-party ad networks. The website http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp provides information regarding this practice by Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") members, and your choices regarding having this information used by these companies, including how to "opt-out" of third-party ad networks operated by NAI members.** You also may contact Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") at http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ for information about opting out of targeted advertising and your choices regarding having information used by DAA member companies, including how to "opt-out" of third-party ad networks operated by DAA members. Opting out of one or more NAI members or DAA members (many of which will be the same) only means that those members no longer will deliver targeted content or ads to you, but it does not mean you will no longer receive any targeted content or ads on our Site or other websites. You may continue to receive advertisements, for example, based on the particular website that you are viewing. Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit this opt-out page, or you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different computer or change web browsers, your NAI or DAA opt-out may no longer, be effective. Additional information is available on NAI's and DAA's websites accessible by the above links.

### Third-Party Links

Our Site may contain, and other visitors may post, links to third-parties. Any access to and use of such linked websites is not governed by this Policy, but, instead, is governed by the privacy policies of those third-party websites, and we are not responsible for the information practices of such third party websites.

### User Generated Content

As stated above, the Site is an open network, and any information that you submit to our Site, unless you have chosen to make that information private, may be viewed by all other visitors to our Site. Users may submit their own content to our Site, including photos, text, and videos. Subject to certain limitations, users may combine that content with other information that is posted to our Site. We are not responsible for the privacy of any information that you choose to post to our Site, our Services, or through any public forum. Nor are we responsible for the accuracy of any information contained in these postings. Any information that you disclose becomes public information. We cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate this Policy, the law, or your personal privacy.

### How Secure Is Information About Me?

We have implemented commercially reasonable precautions, including, where appropriate, password protection, encryption, and SSL to protect our Site and the information we collect from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware that despite our best efforts, no data security measures can guarantee 100% security all of the time.

You should take steps to protect against unauthorized access to your password, phone, and computer by, among other things, signing off after using a shared computer, choosing a password that nobody else knows or can easily guess, and keeping your password private. Also, you should never share your log-in information with others. We are not responsible for any lost, stolen, or compromised passwords or for any activity on your account via unauthorized password activity. To change your Facebook password, you must go to the Facebook site and follow its procedures for changing your password.

### Can I Access and Modify My Personal Information?

You may change your profile picture. You also may delete any content that you have uploaded to our Site. Although the content may be removed from the current, user-accessible portions of our Site and our Services, the content may remain in our systems for a period of time. Please also note that you will not be able to delete content that other users have posted or any content that you have posted that other users have then re-posted or otherwise re-used. 

You also may modify your profile that you have submitted directly to us. 

### What Choices Do I Have?

If we send you any news and newsletters, special offers, promotions or other information we think may interest you, you may tell us to stop sending you such e-mail communications by following the opt-out instructions contained in any such e-mail. Please note that it may take up to 10 business days for us to process opt-out and opt-in requests. Further, if you opt-out of receiving emails about recommendations or other information we think may interest you, we may still send you e-mails about your account or any Services you have requested or received from us.

### Terms of Use

Your use our Site or Services, as well as any dispute over privacy, is subject to this Policy and our Terms of Use.

### How to Contact Us About Privacy

If you have questions about the privacy aspects of our services or would like to make a complaint, please contact us at .

### Changes to this Policy

We may change this Policy from time to time, so be sure to check back periodically. We will post any changes to this Policy to our Site. If we make any changes to this Policy that materially affect our practices with regard to the personal information we have previously collected from you, we will endeavor to provide you with notice in advance of such change by highlighting the change on the Site.
